Lesson 58, a spot of bother.
第58课，一个麻烦的地方。
The old lady was glad to be back at the block of flats where she lived.
这位老太太很高兴回到她居住的公寓街区。
Her shopping had tired her and her basket ad-grown heavier with every step of the way home.
她的购物使她和篮子广告越来越重，回家的每一步。
life: n.   电梯
In the life her thoughts were on lunch and a good rest.
在生活中，她的想法是在午餐和休息良好的生活中。
But when she got out at her own floor, both were forgotten in her sudden discovery that
但是当她在自己的地板上出去时，两人都在突然发现
her front door was open.
她的前门是打开的。
monstrous: adj. 极大的，可怕的
She was thinking that she must reprimand her home health the next morning for such a monstrous
她认为她必须第二天早上谴责自己的家庭健康
peace.
和平。
negligence: n.   粗心大意
Of negligence, when she remembered that she had gone shopping after the home help had
疏忽大意，当她想起自己在家后去购物时
left and she knew that she had turned both keys in their locks.
左，她知道她已经把两个钥匙都插在他们的锁中。
She walked slowly into the hall and at once noticed that all the room doors were open.
她慢慢走进大厅，立刻注意到所有房间的门都是打开的。
Yet following her regular practice she had shut them before going out.
然而，在她的常规练习之后，她在外出之前关闭了它们。
Looking into the drawing room.
看着客厅。
She saw a scene of confusion over by her riding desk.
她在骑行桌上看到了一个混乱的场景。
It was as clear as daylight than that burglars had forced an entry during her absence.
这与日光一样清楚，而小偷在她缺席期间迫使入境。
Her first impulse was to go round all the rooms looking for the thieves.
她的第一个冲动是四处寻找小偷的房间。
prudent: adj. 谨慎的
But then she decided that at her age it might be more prudent to have someone with her.
但是随后她决定，在她的年龄，与她在一起可能会更加谨慎。
So she went to fetch the porter from his basement.
于是她去了他的地下室拿起搬运工。
By this time her legs were beginning to tremble.
到这个时候，她的腿开始颤抖。
So she sat down and accepted a cup of very strong tea.
因此，她坐下来接受了一杯非常强的茶。
While he telephoned the police.
当他打电话给警察时。
composure: n.   镇静，沉着
Then, her composure regained.
然后，她的镇定得以恢复。
intruder: n.   入侵者（尤指欲行窃者）
She was ready to set off with the porter's assistance to search for nay intruders who
她准备出发搬运工的协助，以寻找不在的入侵者
might still.
可能还在。
lurk: v.   潜藏
Be lurking in her flat.
潜伏在她的公寓里。
They went through the rooms.
他们穿过房间。
Being careful to touch nothing.
小心什么都不碰。
hinder: v.   妨碍, fingerprint: n.   指纹
As they did not want to hinder the police in their search for fingerprints.
因为他们不想阻碍警察寻找指纹。
inconceivable: adj. 不可思议的
The chaos was inconceivable.
混乱是不可想象的。
veritable: adj. 真正的，地地道道的, magpie: n.   喜欢收藏物品的人
She had lived in the flat for 30 years and was a veritable magpie at hoarding.
她在公寓里生活了30年，在ho积中是一个名副其实的喜p。
toss: v.   扔
And it seemed as though everything she possessed had been tossed out and turned over and over.
似乎她所拥有的一切都被扔掉，一遍又一遍地翻身。
discard: v.   丢弃
At least sorting out the things she should have discarded years ago was now being made
至少要整理她几年前应该放弃的东西
easier for.
更容易。
constable: n.   警察
Her, then a police inspector arrived with a constable and she told them of her discovery
她，然后一名警察检查员带着警员到达，她告诉他们她的发现
ransack: v.   洗劫
of the ransacked flat.
洗劫公寓的。
fingerprint: n.   指纹
The inspector began to look for fingerprints.
检查员开始寻找指纹。
constable: n.   警察
While the constable checked that the front door locks had not been forced.
当警员检查前门锁是否没有被迫。
balcony: n.   阳台
Thereby proving that the burglars had either used skeleton keys or entered over the balcony.
从而证明了窃贼使用了骨架钥匙，要么在阳台上进入。
fingerprint: n.   指纹
There was no trace of fingerprints.
没有指纹的痕迹。
But the inspector found a dirty red bundle that contained jewelry which the old lady said
但是检查员发现了一个肮脏的红色捆绑包，其中包含珠宝，老太太说
was not.
不是。
Her's.
她的。
So their entry into this flat was apparently not the burglars' first job that day and
因此，他们进入这个公寓的人显然不是那天盗窃者的第一份工作，
they must.
他们必须。
They have been disturbed.
他们被打扰了。
The inspector then asked the old lady to try to check what was missing by the next day
然后，检查员要求老太太尝试检查第二天缺少的东西
and advised.
并建议。
Her not to stay alone in the flat for a few nights.
她不要一个人在公寓里呆几个晚上。
The old lady though there was a fussy creature.
老太太虽然有一个挑剔的生物。
But since the porter agreed with him.
但是自从搬运工同意他以来。
She rang up her daughter and asked for her help in what she described as a little spot
她打了个女儿，在她描述的小地方寻求帮助
of bother.
打扰。